{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "If driving in fog, a driver should turn on the high-beam headlights to increase the field of vision.", "answer": 0, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 16917}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "When driving at night, using the parking lights only is unlawful.", "answer": 1, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 16921}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "There may be times when driving 10 miles per hour is too fast for existing conditions.", "answer": 0, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 16943}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "A driver does not need to allow as much distance when following a motorcycle as when following a car.", "answer": 1, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 16948}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "The best way to avoid loss of control in wet conditions is to speed up:", "answer": 0, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 16974}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "Yield also means stop if you cannot merge safely into the flow of traffic", "answer": 0, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 16989}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "When completing an Emergency Roadside Stop, it is not necessary to put on your parking brake.", "answer": 1, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 17006}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "Because driving involves some risk, it is wise to continually improve your driving and observation skills.", "answer": 0, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 17099}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "Individuals may park in the handicapped parking access aisles located directly beside handicapped parking stalls.", "answer": 0, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 17177}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "It is unlawful to move into the same lane alongside a motorcycle.", "answer": 0, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 17338}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "When passing another vehicle, a driver should wait until the entire car the driver just passed is visible in the rearview mirror before turning back into the right-hand lane.", "answer": 0, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 17354}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "When approaching a railroad crossing that has no warning signals (such as electric flashing lights or gates), a driver should look, listen and slow down.", "answer": 1, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 17364}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "Drivers are not required to yield to pedestrians in a crosswalk.", "answer": 0, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 17395}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "A railroad crossbuck sign should be treated the same as a yield sign.", "answer": 0, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 17414}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "Without exception, never drive a vehicle through, around or under any railroad gate or barrier", "answer": 1, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 17508}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "When driving in fog, you should use your high beam headlights.", "answer": 1, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 17515}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "Only vehicles displaying special plates or parking placards for persons with disabilities may park in spaces reserved for them by an official PARKING FOR PERSONS WITH DISABILITIES sign", "answer": 1, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 17528}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "Motorists are not required to yield to pedestrians when they walk against the traffic light.", "answer": 1, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 17535}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "A driver whose license has been revoked as a result of DUI must meet several requirements, including an evaluation for alcohol and drug problems and paying a reinstatement fee, to regain their license.", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31141}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "An orange sign means drivers should be alert, adjust their speed and be prepared to stop if necessary.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31142}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "A merge sign means drivers should be prepared to change lanes or allow other traffic to come into their lane.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31147}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "It is permissible for anyone to wear a headset while driving.", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31151}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "After making a proper stop and yielding to traffic or pedestrians within the intersection, it is permissible for drivers on a one-way street to turn left at a red light onto another one-way street that moves traffic to the left.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31155}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "If moving with a stream of vehicles across a railroad track, it is safe to stop on the track for a short period of time.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31172}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "Motorcyclists are entitled to use the full width of a traffic lane; therefore, a driver should pass a motorcycle the same way as passing another vehicle.", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31174}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "Drivers may open car doors on the side on which traffic is moving only when it can be done safely and without interfering with traffic.", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31175}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "Drivers must yield to pedestrians in an unmarked crosswalk.", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31178}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "Your driving privileges will be suspended if you are convicted of illegally passing a stopped school bus.", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31205}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "A parent or legal guardian may request that the driver\u2019s license of a minor be cancelled at any time prior to age 18.", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31208}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "Slow vehicles should use the left-hand lane except when passing or making a left turn.", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31210}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "After being pulled over by law enforcement, a driver should immediately exit the vehicle and quickly approach the officer\u2019s squad car.", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31212}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "When approaching a disabled pedestrian using a guide dog, white cane or other assistive device, a driver should yield the right-of-way", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31214}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "Regardless of fault, a crash report must be filed by the driver of a vehicle if the crash involves death, bodily injury or property damage of more than $1,500 (or more than $500 if a vehicle is uninsured).", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31232}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "If arrested with a blood-alcohol concentration of .08 percent or more, an individual's driving privileges will be suspended for at least six months.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31234}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "After a train clears a crossing that has flashing signals, drivers may proceed after checking for a second train on another track and the lights have stopped flashing", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31235}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "If the front right wheel of a vehicle runs off the pavement, a driver should ease off the accelerator, allow the vehicle to slow down, and gently steer back onto the pavement.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31236}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "When experiencing a tire blowout, the driver should apply the brakes quickly and pull off the roadway to check the tire.", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31237}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "The road surface of a bridge may be dangerous in winter because it may remain icy after the rest of the roadway is clear.", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31238}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "Your car must have a horn that can be heard from a distance of 200 feet.", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31265}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "If arrested with a blood-alcohol concentration of .08 percent or more, an individual\u2019s driving privileges will be suspended for at least six months.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31268}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "Drivers may pass on a two-lane roadway marked with a single solid yellow line on their side of the center line.", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31271}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "It is illegal for persons under age 21 to drive with any trace of alcohol or drugs in their system.", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31292}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "When an authorized vehicle using its sirens and flashing lights approaches a vehicle, the driver should pull to the right-hand edge of the roadway and wait for the emergency vehicle to pass.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31293}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "The three-second rule helps the driver determine a safe following distance.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31294}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "A driver may pass another vehicle by driving on the shoulder of the road.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31295}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "If a vehicle starts to skid on water (hydroplane) the driver should quickly apply the brakes.", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31326}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "Headlights must be lighted from sunset to sunrise.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31328}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "During the Initial Licensing Phase, a teen driver is allowed only two passengers under age 20 in the vehicle during the first 12 months of licensing.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31329}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "If a traffic light shows both a red light and a green arrow, a driver may not turn in the direction of the arrow until the red light has changed.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31331}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "A driver who becomes stranded in blizzard conditions should remain in their vehicle.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31354}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "When waiting at an intersection and the traffic signal light turns green, a driver should look to the left and then right before proceeding into the intersection.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31356}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "In order to obtain court supervision for a traffic violation, a minor must appear in court with a parent/legal guardian and attend a traffic safety school.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31360}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "A driver must give the right or left turn signal when changing lanes.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31361}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "Motorcyclists are entitled to use the full width of a traffic lane; therefore, a driver should pass a motorcycle the same way a driver would pass another vehicle.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31384}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "If you are involved in or come upon a traffic crash, you should stop your vehicle in a safe, well-lighted public place that does not obstruct traffic, if able to do so.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31387}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "Alcohol is the single greatest factor in fatal motor vehicle crashes.", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31412}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "When following a vehicle at night it is important to dim your headlights", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31414}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "It is permissible to make a right turn against a red signal light after stopping and yielding to other vehicles and pedestrians.", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31415}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "Illinois law requires that headlights be on when atmospheric conditions require the use of windshield wipers.", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31418}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "Most rear-end collisions are caused by the vehicle in back following too closely.", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31419}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "Driving privileges may be revoked for giving false information to the Secretary of State.", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31442}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "In urban areas, drivers moving out of an alley, building, private road or driveway need not come to a complete stop before entering the roadway if the roadway is clear of traffic", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31443}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "When following a truck at night, it is important to dim your headlights.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31446}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "Cellphone use while driving is permitted as long as the driver is using a hands-free device.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31447}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "Taillights are not required to be illuminated after dark.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31476}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "When on a two-lane roadway, a driver must stop their vehicle when approaching a stopped school bus with its red warning lights flashing and stop signal arm extended.", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31477}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "When a motorist is turning right and a bicyclist is approaching on the right, let the bicyclist go through the intersection first before making a right turn.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31480}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "It is legal for anyone to talk on the phone if using a hands-free device while driving, unless you are under age 19.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31502}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "When approaching a stop sign that is not marked by a crosswalk, drivers should stop their vehicles before entering the intersection.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31503}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "Before a driver can regain driving privileges after losing them for failure to pay damages caused by a crash, the driver must file proof of financial responsibility with the Secretary of State\u2019s office.", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31504}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "When driving in fog a driver should turn on the high-beam headlights to increase the field of vision.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31531}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "T/F Motorcycle drivers must wear a helmet", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 31563}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "T/F Most motorcycle crashes happen on shorts rides", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 31622}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "T/F Motorcycle pasengers must wear a helmet", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 31623}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "T/F The best way to stop quickly is to use both brakes", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 31633}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "When braking you should only use the rear brake", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 31682}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "T/F In Illinois, a person with a BAC of .1 is considered intoxicated.", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 31685}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "When a tire goes flat, yo often hear it", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 31741}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "You do not have to stop for a school bus that is stopped with its red lights flashing if it is on a private road:", "answer": 1, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35757}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "The posted speed limit is the fastest you can drive in the posted area. You must reduce your speed to a lower speed that is safe for the conditions and circumstances that exist whenever necessary.", "answer": 0, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35785}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "Orange is the basic color of signs used in construction work zones to alert drivers.", "answer": 0, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35788}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "Highways and roads freeze before ramps and bridges:", "answer": 0, "state": "me", "type": "permit", "id": 45430}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "The most common mistake that drivers make when backing is failing to look both ways behind them", "answer": 0, "state": "me", "type": "permit", "id": 45844}
{"candidates": ["true", "false"], "question": "Pedestrians in crosswalks and at intersections have the right-of-way over vehicles.", "answer": 0, "state": "me", "type": "permit", "id": 46179}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "You are required to signal anytime you pull away from the curb.", "answer": 0, "state": "me", "type": "permit", "id": 46231}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "While driving at night, you may use your parking lights instead of headlights.", "answer": 1, "state": "me", "type": "permit", "id": 46235}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "A motorist making a left turn at an intersection should yield to the right-of-way to a bicyclist entering the intersection from the opposite direction.", "answer": 0, "state": "me", "type": "permit", "id": 46353}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "Turning left at a red light is never permitted.", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65533}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "Do not pass a school bus when its red lights are flashing.", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65563}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "Children up to age eighteen are prohibited from riding in cargo areas.", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65603}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "A person riding a bicycle has all the same rights, responsibilities and must obey traffic laws as a driver of a motor", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65721}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "When driving in snow or ice conditions, it is safe to use your cruise control as long as your speed is reduced.", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65722}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "When approaching a school bus in the opposite direction, which has its stop lights on and the stop arm extended, on a highway that is divided by a median, you should stop.", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65724}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "Fines for speeding are tripled in work and school zone areas.", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65747}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "Any motor vehicle operator convicted of fleeing in order to avoid arrest for the violation of any Nebraska law can have their license revoked", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65865}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "It is legal to go faster than the speed limit when passing another vehicle.", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65897}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "At intersections with four-way stops, the driver on the right should insist on the right-of-way.", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65900}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "Barricades, vertical panels, drums and cones are the most commonly used devices to guide drivers safely through a work zone.", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65934}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "It is unlawful to operate a motor vehicle upon any public roadway, when such vehicle is equipped with a viewing screen that is visible to the driver.", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 66015}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "A driver that operates a vehicle on Nebraska roadways has already agreed to submit a chemical test or tests when requested by a law enforcement officer.", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 66073}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "Drivers are not required to stop upon meeting a stopped school bus when traveling in the opposite direction on a multi-lane highway.", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96542}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "Drivers must be careful when driving close to cyclist and should maintain a safe operating distance between the motor vehicle and the cyclist.", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96603}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "When driving in fog, you should use your high beam headlights:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96612}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "Drivers must be careful when passing large vehicles and should avoid driving beside a large vehicle for long periods of time:", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96616}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "A motorist making a left turn at an intersection should yield the right-of-way to a bicyclist entering the intersection from the opposite direction.", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96634}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "Blind spots for large vehicles can extend up to 200 feet directly behind the vehicle.", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96699}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "When driving in fog, you should use your low beam headlights:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96723}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "A driver of a vehicle must stop when approaching a stopped school bus unloading children when on a two-lane road.", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96753}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "A driver that operates a vehicle on South Carolina roadways has already agreed to submit a chemical test or tests when requested by a law enforcement officer.", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96754}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "How fast you drive will not affect the distance your vehicle will travel when you need to come to a stop.", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96787}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "When approaching a four way stop, a motorist arriving at the intersection must yield right-of-way to motorists who arrived before him, waiting his turn to enter the intersection.", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96818}
{"candidates": ["True.", "False."], "question": "Motorists are not required to yield to pedestrians when they walk against the traffic light:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96845}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "If you plan to turn your vehicle at an intersection, you should signal 50 - 75 feet before you turn:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96847}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "The faster the speed, the longer it takes to stop when you must react to other driver's unexpected moves.", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96907}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "Talking or texting on a cell phone while driving will not significantly increase your chances for a crash.", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96933}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "Work zones on highways have become increasingly safer for workers and drivers.", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96937}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "Night time is the safest time for cyclists to ride their bikes.", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96939}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "The presence of double yellow lines means you may pass another vehicle from either direction.", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96945}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "Drivers are required to stop for a stopped school bus when driving on a two-lane road.", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97003}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "It is unlawful to move into the same lane alongside a motorcycle:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97024}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "A person riding a bicycle has all the same rights and responsibilities and must obey traffic laws as a driver of a motor vehicle.", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97027}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "A driver of a vehicle need not stop upon meeting a stopped school bus when traveling in the opposite direction on a multi-lane highway or multi-lane private road.", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97028}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "When driving through a neighborhood, the speed limit is usually 30 mph.", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97091}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "It is illegal to use a radar detector in Virginia", "answer": 1, "state": "va", "type": "permit", "id": 110675}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "You must use your headlights whenever you use your windshield wipers as a result of bad weather", "answer": 1, "state": "va", "type": "permit", "id": 110706}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "The $500 uninsured motor vehicle fee provides basic liability insurance coverage", "answer": 0, "state": "va", "type": "permit", "id": 110707}
{"candidates": ["over age 21", "under age 21"], "question": "Vertical driver's licenses are issued to persons", "answer": 1, "state": "va", "type": "permit", "id": 110768}
{"candidates": ["True", "False"], "question": "Cell phones can be a serious source of driver distractions", "answer": 0, "state": "va", "type": "permit", "id": 110887}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "When driving from a private road or driveway, you do not have to stop before crossing a sidewalk", "answer": 0, "state": "va", "type": "permit", "id": 110949}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "It is legal to transport children under age 16 in the bed of a pick-up truck if it is equipped with a camper shell", "answer": 0, "state": "va", "type": "permit", "id": 111034}
{"candidates": ["False", "True"], "question": "Drivers are responsible for making sure that children are properly secured in vehicles", "answer": 1, "state": "va", "type": "permit", "id": 111039}
